Wendy's has the hottest drink on the market right now.
There is a drink that sold more than 10,000 times in 10 days after its release!
It's a big hit right out of the gate!
When you drink it, you'll see
It's so soft and soft!
The secret is
It contains fungui, a traditional Taiwanese sweet.
Funggui is a Taiwanese sweet made from sweet potato flour and potato starch.
made from sweet potato flour and potato starch.
The texture of the fungui is its special feature.
The drink is a blend of three kinds of black tea
with a generous amount of passion fruit added to it!
We sold 10,000 bottles of this new drink in 10 days!
It's very refreshing!
The crunchy texture of the passion fruit and the puffy texture of the pungui are fun!
Today, check out a drink that allows you to enjoy the crunchy texture of pungui and crunchy fruit!
You can enjoy it at Gong Cha.
It is easy to drink and refreshing with a very summery color!
That's the colorful frozen tea!
Crunchy!
It is very cold and crunchy!
At the bottom is
Crunchy!
The frozen drink poured on top of it
It is a cool drink inspired by the midsummer sky.
The refreshing Blue Hawaii with a hint of tea flavor.
The crunchy texture and the jelly pulls together to create a fun texture.
Good night!
Flippers is popular for its fluffy pancakes
There is a drink that has sold more than 500 pans in two weeks!
That's it!
White sugar squash!
A refreshing thirst-quenching squash
It is made with raw syrup made from white sugar produced in Shinshun
You can enjoy the original sweetness of peaches in the syrup
Add plenty of ice.
Lemon slices are used to add a touch of sourness.
And finally, top with white peach sorbet and nata de coco for a delightful crunchy texture, and you have the perfect summer squash! Add to this the white peach sorbet and nata de coco topping, and you have the perfect summer squash!
The peach sorbet and nata de coco give the squash a refreshing and light taste. You can enjoy this drink at the popular fruit tart store, Quilfebont.
This is a drink that you can enjoy at KIRPHEBON, a popular fruit tart shop.
The drink is actually a pineapple frappe with mild custard and sour pineapple, inspired by the very popular pineapple tart.
It is then mixed with ice and finished with pineapple and
Powdered tart dough is sprinkled over the top to make it taste like a popular tart.
The result is a crispy drink that tastes just like the popular tart!
Very fruity!
The sweet custard and sweet and sour pineapple are a perfect match!
Perfect for the hot summer season!
Thank you very much for watching this video!
Please like, comment and subscribe to our channel!
Thank you!
This is Fuji TV announcer, Shinichi Kalbe
Seika Inoue, Fuji TV announcer
Thank you very much.